Well. I hope
to see everyone tonight
at the school dance.
The Dance Committee
worked really hard
decorating the gym. okay?
Hey. are you dorks
going to the dance?
Uh. no.
We're gonna drink beer
and kick some ass.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
drinking beer and kicking ass.
Yeah.
Um. Butt-Head.
we don't have any beer.
We don't have any ass either.
Go kick that grasshopper's ass
while I figure out
how to get some beer.
Okay. um...
Let's see. um...
which part is his ass?
Okay. here we go.
Butt-Head. help!
You got some insect pests
in your lot there. do you?
Uh. can you. like. shut up?
Beavis is trying to kick
this bug's ass.
Well. that's not
gonna get rid of 'em.
You need some pesticide.
Here. follow me.
Yeah. the American pesticides
don't work anymore
because of the goddamn
hippie environmentalists.
so I drove down to Mexico
and got some
good. old fashioned DDT.
It's getting so Mexico
is the only place
you can be an American anymore.
Yeah. just don't touch it now.
It's real poisonous.
What is that stuff?
Uh. well. let's see.
That says something in Spanish.
Uh. and that's a fly.
Whoa. Spanish. fly.
This is Spanish fly.
Um. and what's that?
That's. like. a "after-disiac"
It. like. makes people
who want to drink it
want to score.
Yeah.
but I already want to score.
So do I. Beavis.
but wouldn't it be
a better world if everyone
was like us?
Oh. yeah. yeah. yeah.
then everyone
would be scoring all the time.
Yeah.
Beavis. we could make
the world a better place.
Those are two good boys
out there. I tell you what.
Not like those other two
who live around here.
Travis and Burt.
Mm-hmm.
This is gonna be cool.
Before we set off
on our journey.
let's relax and get comfortable.
You may notice your breath.
Boy. this guy is a creepy perv.
You may notice
your head and neck
relaxing onto your pillow...
You may notice yourself
watching a horrible.
boring video that sucks.
This reminds me
of that pervy guy
at the model train store
that always takes you camping.
Shut up. Butt-Head.
He's not pervy.
And you may not notice my hands
even getting lower.
Shut up. Butt-Head.
He's just a little handsy.
You know. he just likes
to sniff hair
and rub shoulders
and stuff like that. you know.
This evening
on the way to sleep.
we'll be travelling
from Rouen to Evreux.
We'll be traveling
from "rugh" to "abugh"
Yeah. and we'll be stopping off
at "bleugh-ugh"...
To use the bathroom
and have a shake or something.
What language is that?
Uh. I think it's. like. French.
Oh. yeah. yeah.
I think. to speak French.
you have to. like.
drink a bunch of milk
and get all this. like.
phlegm in your throat
so you can start going
Yeah. yeah.
Whoa. that's pretty good. Beavis.
Where did you learn to do that?
Um. my grandpa
used to speak French
when he got up in the morning.
He'd be like...
And also. like.
once a week when he was locked
in the room with Grandma.
Ooh. ah. ooh.
Bleh. bleh. ugh. ugh!
Uh. so what does that mean?
I think he was saying. like.
"This sucks" or something.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Spanish fly is cool.
I think it. like.
melted my shoe or something.
You won't need that shoe
when you score. Beavis.
Yeah. everyone in the school
is gonna drink this stuff.
and then
everyone is gonna score.
Yeah.
Shoes will become
a thing of the past.
Yeah. yeah. and pants too.
They will call us heroes.
You know. Butt-Head.
I just wanna say. um.
it feels really good
to do something nice
for other people.
You know what I mean?
Now let's give it
a little flavor here.
Huh.
Where'd it go?
Um. I think my foot is bleeding.
Just look at
all those people. Beavis.
They have no idea that tonight
they shall score.
This is the most nicest thing
we have ever done.
I don't even need anyone
to thank us. yeah.
Just feels good to do it.
you know?
That's right. Beavis.
Everyone having sex
with each other
right here in the gym
will be its own reward.
Yeah. yeah. this is
the true meaning of Christmas.
Yeah.
Um. Butt-Head. do you think
it might run out later.
and then we don't get any.
and then we don't get to score?
Uh. I don't know.
I'm gonna have a little now
just in case.
Ugh.
Good idea.
Ooh!
Um. Butt-Head.
it doesn't taste very good.
That's the taste of scoring. dumbass.
and if you don't like it.
then maybe scoring's
not for you.
Ugh!
No.
No. I like it.
It tastes good.
I think it was just
that damn orange
I put in there.
Yeah. that's good.
I think it's. like.
scoring in my mouth
or something maybe.
I don't know. hm.
Uh. you drank more than me. butthole.
Now we're even.
- No way. Butt-Head!
That was more than me!
Ugh. ah!
Now we're even. yeah.
- No. we're not.
You didn't count that stuff
that was on your shoe.
No way. Butt-Head.
that's not fair.
Uh. I don't feel so good.
Yeah. me too. yeah.
Maybe we'll feel better
after we score.
Oh. yeah.
Help yourself
to some punch. ladies.
It'll make the world
a better place.
Uh. wait a minute.
some greedy butthole
drank it all.
You know. you know.
some people just don't care
about others. you know?
It's sad.
Oh. what happened
to the festive punch I made?
There was organic apple juice
in it and...
Oh. my.
Breakfast sucks.
I mean. it's not
my favorite meal.
but. um. I'd say
it's in my top three.
She needs. like.
more auto-tune on her voice.
Yeah. I don't think
that's auto-tune. Butt-Head.
That's just the way she sings.
I can do that.
Yeah.
Uh. really?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
anyone can do it.
Yeah. yeah. check it out.
See?
Whoa.
How do you do that?
You know. you just
sort of. like. um...
you just sort of do
an auto-tune thing. you know?
You just kind of go like...
Uh. hm.
Let me try it.
No. no. you're not
doing it right. Butt-Head.
That sounded as good as yours.
No. no. it didn't.
Sorry. Butt-Head. it didn't.
Uh. yeah. it was.
Shut up. dumbass.
I can show you how to do it.
You just want to. like.
move your throat
and. like. your lips
and your mouth
and kind of change the notes
in the...
Well. like this.
Watch really close here. okay?
Ooh. that was horrible.
Butt-head.
Damn it. Beavis.
I'm gonna auto-tune
the backside of your head.
Whoa. that sounded
pretty good. Beavis.
I'm gonna try it again.
Ugh!
The DDT gave them
massive brain damage.
It's amazing
they have enough brain function
to still be alive.
Actually. Doctor.
these scans are from before
they drank the DDT.
These boys were here a month ago
to have objects removed
from their nasal cavities.
Uh. those were army men. yeah.
They made
the ultimate sacrifice.
Oh. then I guess
we're done here.
Oh. boy.
Nobody scored.
did they Butt-Head?
No.
But at least we learned
a lesson.
That doing things
for other people sucks?
Yep. but don't worry. Beavis.
We will never do it again
as long as we live.
Amen. yeah.
Chirp.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm